import {UnderlineText, SquareRoot, superscript, subscript, BoldText, ItalicText, Fraction, ShortFraction, LongFraction, MixedFraction, Isotopes } from "@/mathnotation"

export const ENGLISHLANGUAGEA2005 = [






{
instruction: "In each of the following sentence, there is one word or group of words underlined word and one gap. From the list of words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the one that is most nearly opposito in meaning to the underlined word or group of words and that will, at the hame time, correctly fill the gap in the sentence.",
id: "question1",
question: ["1. The management has neither _________________ nor ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"denied"}/>, " the rumour that it was going to lay off some workers."],
A: "pronounced",
B: "confirmed",
C: "rejected",
D: "advertised",
answer: "B. confirmed",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question2",
question: ["2. Instead of _________________ the issue, the speaker ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"digressed"}/>, " to unimportant matters."],
A: "summarizing",
B: "describing",
C: "revealing",
D: "addressing",
answer: "D. addressing",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question3",
question: ["3. The telephone booths were all _________________ and I had to wait for more than ten minutes for one to become ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"vacant."}/>, ""],
A: "locked",
B: "busy",
C: "occupied",
D: "ringing",
answer: "C. occupied",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question4",
question: ["4. While the first battalion ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"halted"}/>, " its march at nightfall, the second _________________ to the barracks _________________ "],
A: "returned",
B: "set out",
C: "proceeded",
D: "turned up",
answer: "C. proceeded",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question5",
question: ["5. His father is an _________________ driver but he is only a ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"novice."}/>, ""],
A: "enlightened",
B: "aged",
C: "excellent",
D: "experienced.",
answer: "D. experienced",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question6",
question: ["6. The arrival of the police at the scene _________________ rather than ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"mitigated"}/>, " tension."],
A: "provoked",
B: "enlightened",
C: "created",
D: "prolonged.",
answer: "C. created",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question7",
question: ["7. Roses are ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"common"}/>, " in May but _________________ in November."],
A: "dead",
B: "strange",
C: "rare",
D: "extinct.",
answer: "C. rare",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question8",
question: ["8. A bank clerk should be able to tell easily the difference between _________________ notes and ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"counterfeit"}/>, " ones."],
A: "crisp",
B: "good",
C: "correct",
D: "genuine.",
answer: "D. genuine",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question9",
question: ["9. Last night, Uncle Joe was blind ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"drunk"}/>, " but this morning he is as _________________ as a judge."],
A: "alert",
B: "saintly",
C: "strong",
D: "sober.",
answer: "D. sober",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question10",
question: ["10. What I have is only a _________________ of the famous painting; the ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"original"}/>, " is in the National Museum."],
A: "duplicate",
B: "model",
C: "fake",
D: "drawing.",
answer: "B. model",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "2",
sectiontitle: "From the words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the word or group of words thatsbeht completes each of the following sentences",
id: "question11",
question: "11. If the jury's verdict is 'not guilty,' the defendant will be",
A: "acquitted",
B: "indicted",
C: "pardoned",
D: "forgiven.",
answer: "A. acquitted",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question12",
question: "12. When all the items on the agenda had been discussed, the meeting was _________________ .",
A: "adjourned",
B: "dismissed",
C: "postponed",
D: "dissolved.",
answer: "A. adjourned",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question13",
question: "13. Because the new venture was _________________ many businessmen and women went into it.",
A: "rich",
B: "manageable",
C: "lucrative",
D: "satisfying.",
answer: "C. lucrative",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question14",
question: "14. We saw a _________________ of lions at the game reserve.",
A: "pride",
B: "family",
C: "band",
D: "group.",
answer: "A. pride",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question15",
question: "15. Many educationists feel that _________________ punishment should still be retained in schools.",
A: "capital",
B: "corporate",
C: "sincere",
D: "physical",
answer: "B. corporate",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question16",
question: "16. Freedom of movement is a _________________ right of every citizen.",
A: "fundamental",
B: "negotiated",
C: "privileged",
D: "respected",
answer: "A. fundamental",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question17",
question: "17. The river _________________ towards the sea.",
A: "meandered",
B: "rolled",
C: "ran",
D: "trickled.",
answer: "A. meandered",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question18",
question: "18. I _________________ that our team will win the match tomorrow.",
A: "certify",
B: "conclude",
C: "announce",
D: "predict.",
answer: "D. predict",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question19",
question: "19. If found guilty, he will _________________ all the wealth he has amassed illegally.",
A: "forgo",
B: "abandon",
C: "repay",
D: "forfeit.",
answer: "D. forfeit",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question20",
question: "20. At a _________________ of 200 kilometres an hour, the hurricane swept away everything in its path.",
A: "movement",
B: "flow",
C: "velocity",
D: "drive.",
answer: "C. velocity",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "3",
sectiontitle: "After each of the following sentences, a list of possible interpretations is given. Choose the interpretation that you consider most appropriate for each sentence.",
id: "question21",
question: "21. Ladies and gentlemen, the worst may be over, but we are not out of the woods yet. This means that we are _________________ ",
A: "still in the forest",
B: "not yet ready to celebrate our success",
C: "likely to encounter more difficulties",
D: "not sure of ourselves",
answer: "C. likely to encounter more difficulties",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question22",
question: "22. When I leave this country it will be for good. This means that I will _________________ ",
A: "never come back",
B: "leave for better conditions elsewhere",
C: "become an adventurer",
D: "improve my ways",
answer: "A. never come back",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question23",
question: "23. When she confronted her husband, he hung his head and didn't answer her questions. This means that he was _________________ ",
A: "defiant",
B: "ashamed and embarrassed",
C: "caught unawares",
D: "angry with her",
answer: "B. ashamed and embarrassed",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question24",
question: "24. All our plans fell through at the last moment. This means that we _________________ ",
A: "were exposed",
B: "delayed",
C: "were abandoned",
D: "failed.",
answer: "D. failed",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question25",
question: "25. The police knew that the suspect was not being straight with them. This means that the suspect was _________________ ",
A: "not telling the truth",
B: "not friendly",
C: "afraid",
D: "timid.",
answer: "A. not telling the truth",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question26",
question: "26. After his prison experience, Etim decided to go straight. This mean that he decided to _________________ ",
A: "hold his head up and walk with defiance",
B: "change his religion",
C: "live an honest life",
D: "stop using drugs",
answer: "C. live an honest life",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question27",
question: "27. The teacher spoke with his tongue in his cheek when he said that lazy Ade was the best pupil. This means that the teacher _________________ ",
A: "did not mean what he said",
B: "was disappointed",
C: "was angry",
D: "tried to encourage",
answer: "A. did not mean what he said",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question28",
question: "28. They did not know what to expect and so decided to play it by ear. This means that they decided to _________________ .",
A: "listen attentively to everyone",
B: "act according to circumstances",
C: "pretend to be deaf",
D: "prepare for the worst.",
answer: "B. act according to circumstances",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question29",
question: "29. Ojo decided that the best course of acting was to play along with them for the time being. This means that he decided to _________________ .",
A: "join their team temporarily",
B: "entertain them for a while",
C: "pretend to agree with them",
D: "be playful with them",
answer: "C. pretend to agree with them",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question30",
question: "30. The conference was attended by people from all walks of life. This means that the conference was attended by people _________________ ",
A: "of all races",
B: "who had travelled widely",
C: "from all professions",
D: "from different parts of the world",
answer: "C. from all professions",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "4",
sectiontitle: "From the words or group of words lettered A to D below each of the following sentences, choose the word or group of words that is noarost in moaning to the underlined word or group of words ah it is uhed in the sentence",
id: "question31",
question: ["31. Amina is the one who ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"initiated"}/>, " the quarrel, not Nike!"],
A: "started",
B: "stopped",
C: "settled",
D: "fuelled.",
answer: "A. started",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question32",
question: ["32. She was ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"reprimanded"}/>, " by her boss for negligence."],
A: "sacked.",
B: "rebuked",
C: "punished",
D: "surcharged.",
answer: "B. rebuked",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question33",
question: ["33. Why should I ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"retract"}/>, " my statement when it is nothing but the truth?"],
A: "alter",
B: "deny",
C: "withdraw.",
D: "condemn.",
answer: "C. withdraw",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question34",
question: ["34. The doctor diagnosed the tumour as ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"malignant."}/>, ""],
A: "deadly",
B: "painful",
C: "infectious",
D: "minor.",
answer: "A. deadly",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question35",
question: ["35. In tropical Africa, mosquitoes are ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"ubiquitous."}/>, ""],
A: "dangerous.",
B: "harmful",
C: "trouble",
D: "everywhere.",
answer: "D. everywhere",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question36",
question: ["36. It soon became obvious that a confrontation was ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"inevitable."}/>, ""],
A: "disastrous",
B: "unavoidable",
C: "desirable",
D: "imminent.",
answer: "B. unavoidable",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question37",
question: ["37. They insisted that the omission of my name had been ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"inadvertent."}/>, ""],
A: "unintentional",
B: "unconditional",
C: "improper",
D: "unfortunate.",
answer: "A. unintentional",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question38",
question: ["38. The police announced that they were yet to ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"apprehend"}/>, " the criminals."],
A: "interrogate",
B: "charge.",
C: "prosecute",
D: "arrest.",
answer: "D. arrest",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question39",
question: ["39. He is easily recognisable because of a ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"conspicuous"}/>, " birthmark on his face."],
A: "dark",
B: "beautiful",
C: "noticeable",
D: "natural",
answer: "C. noticeable",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question40",
question: ["40. The fishing boat was ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"imperilled"}/>, " by high winds, but it managed to reach port safely."],
A: "pushed",
B: "endangered",
C: "disturbed",
D: "blown.",
answer: "B. endangered",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "5",
sectiontitle: "From the words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the word or group of words that bost completes each of the following sentences",
id: "question41",
question: "41. Surprisingly, Musa turned _________________ the job.",
A: "away",
B: "in",
C: "out",
D: "down.",
answer: "D. down",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question42",
question: "42. We have no choice _________________ to do what they demand.",
A: "except",
B: "than",
C: "unless",
D: "but.",
answer: "B. than",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question43",
question: "43. The committee has submitted its report _________________ the students' riot.",
A: "in",
B: "for",
C: "about",
D: "on.",
answer: "D. on",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question44",
question: "44. The chairman told members that he was open _________________ suggestions.",
A: "to",
B: "for",
C: "about",
D: "on",
answer: "A. to",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question45",
question: "45. The policeman shot the escaping robber _________________ the leg.",
A: "on",
B: "in",
C: "at",
D: "into.",
answer: "C. at",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question46",
question: "46. For the management, your remarks amount to a slap _________________ the face.",
A: "on",
B: "upon",
C: "at",
D: "in",
answer: "D. in",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question47",
question: "47. She does not remember _________________ to anyone at the park.",
A: "to talk",
B: "to be talking",
C: "talking",
D: "to have talked.",
answer: "C. talking",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question48",
question: "48. This portion is to be shared between _________________ ",
A: "us and them",
B: "we and them",
C: "us and they",
D: "we and they.",
answer: "A. us and them",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question49",
question: "49. Joel is one of those fanatical sports fans _________________ about nothing else.",
A: "who talks",
B: "who talked",
C: "who talk",
D: "who is talking",
answer: "A. who talks",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question50",
question: "50. I will see you _________________ tomorrow.",
A: "when I return",
B: "after I have returned",
C: "after I might have returned",
D: "when I have returned.",
answer: "A. when I return",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question51",
question: "51. But for the night guard's vigilance, the factory _________________ burgled.",
A: "would be",
B: "will be",
C: "would have been",
D: "will have been",
answer: "C. would have been",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question52",
question: "52. No sooner _________________ it started to rain.",
A: "did he arrive home when",
B: "had he arrived home than",
C: "than he arrived home",
D: "when he arrive home.",
answer: "B. had he arrived home than",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question53",
question: "53. Hardly a day goes by _________________ he doesn't think of her.",
A: "that",
B: "when",
C: "while",
D: "without.",
answer: "A. that",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question54",
question: "54. Scarcely had I opened the door _________________ the dog came running in.",
A: "as",
B: "before",
C: "than",
D: "when.",
answer: "D. when",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question55",
question: "55. Several _________________ attended that two-day summit.",
A: "head of state",
B: "heads of states",
C: "heads of state",
D: "head of states",
answer: "C. heads of state",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question56",
question: "56. You haven't seen this man before? _________________ ",
A: "isn't it so",
B: "have you",
C: "is it so",
D: "isn't it.",
answer: "B. have you",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question57",
question: "57. I saw him again _________________ last week.",
A: "some time",
B: "sometimes",
C: "one time",
D: "sometime.",
answer: "D. sometime",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question58",
question: "58. She bought a _________________ handbag.",
A: "red beautiful leather",
B: "beautiful leather red",
C: "beautiful red leather",
D: "leather beautiful red",
answer: "C. beautiful red leather",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question59",
question: "59. It was the head-boy that took the book away _________________ ?",
A: "didn't he",
B: "wasn't he",
C: "wasn't it",
D: "isn't it",
answer: "B. wasn't he",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question60",
question: "60. _________________ my father took me to England",
A: "At the aged of ten",
B: "Being ten years old",
C: "When I was ten",
D: "At ten years old.",
answer: "A. At the aged of ten",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question61",
question: "61. The teacher wanted to know if all our homework _________________ submitted.",
A: "have been",
B: "has been",
C: "had been",
D: "is being.",
answer: "C. had been",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question62",
question: "62. The man denied _________________ the company's property.",
A: "stolen",
B: "to have stolen",
C: "to be stealing",
D: "stealing.",
answer: "D. stealing",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question63",
question: "63. The day I won a visa lottery was the _________________ day of my life.",
A: "happy",
B: "very happy",
C: "happiest",
D: "happier.",
answer: "C. happiest",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question64",
question: "64. Ebiere invited _________________ to her birthday party",
A: "Bola and I",
B: "myself and Bola",
C: "Bola and me",
D: "Bola and myself",
answer: "C. Bola and me",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question65",
question: "65. The company employs only experienced _________________ mature workers.",
A: "and",
B: "but",
C: "well",
D: "very.",
answer: "A. and",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question66",
question: "66. Adamu looked at his watch and said: 'It's high time we _________________ home.'",
A: "must go",
B: "went",
C: "should go",
D: "go",
answer: "B. went",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question67",
question: "67. She claims _________________ a ghost last night.",
A: "seeing",
B: "to be seeing",
C: "to have seen",
D: "having seen",
answer: "C. to have seen",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question68",
question: "68. We had better _________________ now, or we'll miss the train.",
A: "left",
B: "leave",
C: "be leaving",
D: "to leave.",
answer: "B. leave",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question69",
question: "69. She _________________ the sleeping baby on the bed.",
A: "lay",
B: "lies",
C: "lied",
D: "laid.",
answer: "D. laid",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question70",
question: "70 _________________ we rather go home? he asked.",
A: "Shouldn't",
B: "Can't",
C: "Won't",
D: "mustn't.",
answer: "B. Can't",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question71",
question: "71. I know that song very well; we _________________ it everyday when I was in primary school.",
A: "sang",
B: "had sung",
C: "have sung",
D: "sing.",
answer: "A. sang",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question72",
question: "72. They _________________ the competition when we arrived.",
A: "begun",
B: "have begun",
C: "had begun",
D: "begin.",
answer: "C. had begun",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question73",
question: "73. If you _________________ early, you will get there before nightfall.",
A: "left",
B: "are leaving",
C: "had left",
D: "leave.",
answer: "D. leave",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question74",
question: "74. The test was so difficult that _________________ students passed.",
A: "some few",
B: "a few",
C: "few",
D: "fewest.",
answer: "C. few",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question75",
question: "75. Please can you _________________ money?",
A: "lend me little",
B: "lend me some",
C: "lend me some",
D: "borrow me some.",
answer: "C. lend me some",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question76",
question: "76. _________________ at 5 o' clock every morning was one of the regulations he detested most at school.",
A: "To be waking up",
B: "Waking up",
C: "Having to be waking up",
D: "To be waking.",
answer: "B. Waking up",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question77",
question: "77. If you had waited five minutes longer, you her _________________ ",
A: "would be able to see",
B: "will be able to see",
C: "would have been able to see",
D: "will have seen",
answer: "C. would have been able to see",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question78",
question: "78. She asked the driver to _________________ at the school gate.",
A: "drop her",
B: "drop her down",
C: "drop her out",
D: "drop her in.",
answer: "A. drop her",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question79",
question: "79. She told me that she always _________________ the television before going to bed.",
A: "switch off",
B: "off",
C: "switched off",
D: "switches off.",
answer: "A. switch off",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question80",
question: "80. I _________________ the new principal, Obi said",
A: "look forward to meet",
B: "look forward to having met",
C: "am looking forward to meeting",
D: "am looking forward to meet.",
answer: "C. am looking forward to meeting",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
passage: "Birds are instantly recognizable -81-, perhaps because of their ability to -82-. Some people might consider their shape the most distinguishing -83-. Everyone, however, agrees on the characteristics that a bird possesses: two -84-, feathers, two legs, a toothless -85-, warm blood, and the ability to - 86- eggs. The modern system of 87- birds is like a pyramid, with the base formed by 8,514 different -88-. A convenient -89- of this system recognizes a group of birds which does not normally -90- with other groups.",
id: "question81",
question: "81. *********************",
A: "beings",
B: "creatures",
C: "things",
D: "mammals",
answer: "B. creatures",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question82",
question: "82. *********************",
A: "Soar",
B: "dive",
C: "glide",
D: "fly",
answer: "D. fly",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question83",
question: "83. *********************",
A: "possession",
B: "mark",
C: "feature",
D: "sign",
answer: "C. feature",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question84",
question: "84. *********************",
A: "arms",
B: "flaps",
C: "forearms",
D: "wings.",
answer: "D. wings",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question85",
question: "85. *********************",
A: "mouth",
B: "lip",
C: "beak",
D: "gum",
answer: "C. beak",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question86",
question: "86. *********************",
A: "produce",
B: "provide",
C: "lay",
D: "give",
answer: "C. lay",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question87",
question: "87. *********************",
A: "classifying",
B: "arranging",
C: "ordering",
D: "numbering",
answer: "C. ordering",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question88",
question: "88. *********************",
A: "species",
B: "birds",
C: "types",
D: "varieties",
answer: "A. species",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question89",
question: "89. *********************",
A: "judgement",
B: "explanation",
C: "statement",
D: "name.",
answer: "B. explanation",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question90",
question: "90. *********************",
A: "agree",
B: "mate",
C: "fly",
D: "go.",
answer: "B. mate",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
passage: "One of the most precious gifts human kind has been given is the power to -91-. With it, we pass vital -92- to one another either -93- or by non-vocal methods, such as -94-. Freedom of -9w5-e1 psa, sIsn fact, a widely contested issue throughout the world. Some have therefore, assumed that communication is the -96- of only humans. Yet, research shows that animals -97- information in intricate ways often baffle humans. Yes, they 'speak, not with words, but through visual signals such as -98- tails, twitching ears, or -99- wings. Other forms of animal communication may involve the use of voice, such as a bark, a roar, a snarl, or -100-. Some of the languages are obvious to humans, while others require much scientific study to detect.",
id: "question91",
question: "91. *********************",
A: "communication",
B: "inform",
C: "tell",
D: "say",
answer: "A. communication",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question92",
question: "92. *********************",
A: "news",
B: "words",
C: "things",
D: "information",
answer: "D. information",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question93",
question: "93. *********************",
A: "quickly",
B: "verbally",
C: "secretly",
D: "symbolically",
answer: "B. verbally",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question94",
question: "94. *********************",
A: "smiling",
B: "nodding",
C: "gestures",
D: "winkling",
answer: "D. winkling",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question95",
question: "95. *********************",
A: "speaking",
B: "speech",
C: "saying",
D: "expressing.",
answer: "B. speech",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question96",
question: "96. *********************",
A: "preserve",
B: "belonging",
C: "property",
D: "policy",
answer: "A. preserve",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question97",
question: "97. *********************",
A: "give",
B: "receive",
C: "handle",
D: "exchange",
answer: "D. exchange",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question98",
question: "98. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "C. wagging",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question99",
question: "99. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "B. flapping",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question100",
question: "100. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "C. whistling",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},



]